# **Elliot Moore**

# **DATA ANALYST**

Brentwood TN, 37027 | apcsmoore@gmail.com | <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/elliot-e-moore/">https://github.com/Elliot-Moore</a> | (615) 212-5757

I've been fascinated with data since a young age when I stumbled upon a World Almanac. I prefer to approach obstacles from many different perspectives, but once decided I push to see them done in an efficient and speedy manner. I enjoy singing and playing chess in my free time.

#### **SKILLS**

- Excel (VLOOKUP, PowerPivot, Pivot Tables)
- SQL (PostgreSQL, JOINS)
- Power BI/Tableau

- Python (Pandas)
- Git/Github

# **DATA EXPERIENCE**

Nashville Software School

Data Analytics Apprentice September 2021 – Present

Full-Time, 5- month program analyzing, manipulating, and presenting large amounts of data using Excel, SQL, PowerBI / Tableau, and Python. Work is structured in single and group projects mimicking real world tasks.

## **Projects**

Lahman Baseball Project: Using data from Lahman's Baseball Database, answered baseball related questions such as, "Does a correlation exist between team salary and team success?" and "Are left handed pitchers more decorated than right handed ones?" by retrieving and joining data from many different tables. Wrote significant portions of SQL queries and provided further analysis with Excel. As team lead, ensured group members worked in tandem and understood all concepts covered within the project using agile workflow.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Amazon Inc.

#### **Learning Ambassador**

April 2020 – June 2021

- Used company software to manage significant portions of a delivery center, including package induct, package stow, route picking, route staging, route departures, and crash sorts.
- Ensured company rates were met or exceeded and safety was maintained.
- Cultivated an instructive and helpful demeanor to mentor less experienced employees while also helping maintain a team dynamic with the associates I was responsible for.

Kroger Inc.

#### **Self Checkout Attendant**

May 2018 - August 2018

- Supervised a cluster of self-checkout machines at the front end of a Kroger.
- Endeavoured to greet every customer using the self checkouts and rapidly respond to customers needing assistance.
- Fixed minor hardware/software issues with the self-checkout apparatus.

Publix Inc.

# **Produce Stocker**

May 2016 - August 2016

Stocked produce section of a Publix, keeping shelves clean and tidy.

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

Nashville Software School | Nashville, TN | Data Analytics Certification | Expected Graduation Date: Jan 2022 University of Alabama | Tuscaloosa, AL | Some college with a focus on Civil Engineering Brentwood High School | Brentwood, TN | High School Diploma